var questions = [
  {
      question: "1. Commonly used data types DO NOT include:",
      choices: [ "strings",  "booleans", "alerts", "numbers"],
      answer: "alerts"
    },
    {
      question: "2. The condition in an if / else statement is enclosed within ____.",
      choices: ["quotes", "curly brackets", "parentheses", "square brackets"],
      answer: "parentheses"
    },
    {
      question: "3. Which symbol is used for single-line comment in JavaScript:",
      choices: ["/%", "//", "{}", "[]"],
      answer: "//"
    },
    {
      question: "4. Which operator check for equality in value: ",
      choices: ["===", "++", "&&", "=="],
      answer: "=="
    },
    {
      question: "5. Which on is a looping structure:",
      choices: ["for", "render", "init", "loop"],
      answer: "for"
    },
    {
      question: "6. Which keyword refers to the object from where it is called:",
      choices: ["call", "init", "onClick", "this"],
      answer: "this"
    },
    {
      question: "7. Variable: Error when attempting to read value:",
      choices: ["undeclared", "undefined", "declared", "variable"],
      answer: "undeclared"
    },
    {
      question: "8. Timers in JavaScript use:",
      choices: ["setTimeout", "intervalClear", "timer", "countdown"],
      answer: "setInterval"
    },
  
    {
      question: "9. How do you find the operating system using JavaScript:",
      choices: ["os.version", "nav.appversion", "append.navigator", "navigator.appversion"],
      answer: "navigation.appversion"
    },
    {
      question: "10. What is a text box provided to user for user-input to enter either a text or number:",
      choices: ["input label", "alert box", "input box", "prompt box"],
      answer: "prompt box",
     
    },
    
  
];

